(Leonard:)You know,
I'm happy that Penny's moving on.
It gives me freedom to move on myself.
(Howard:)Are you saying
that you've been holding back?
(Leonard:)Of course. Out of respect.
(Howard:)So how do you explain
the 10 years before Penny?
(Raj:)Who were you respecting then?
(Leonard:)What? I've dated plenty of women.
There was, uh, Joyce Kim,
Leslie Winkle...
(Sheldon:)Notify the editors
of the Oxford English Dictionary:
The word "plenty"
has been redefined to mean "two."
(Leonard:)What about that girl last year
at Comic-Con?
- It doesn't count.
- Why not?
(Raj:)What happens in costume at Comic-Con
stays at Comic-Con.
(Howard:)You're only saying that
because of what happened.
- What happened to you?
- Nothing happened to me.
(Howard:)It wasn't your fault, Raj.
(Howard:)He was dressed
as a green Orion slave girl.
How did we get on me?
We were mocking Leonard.